

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer (LARAVEL, MySQL, ReactJs)

Shebaru IT

03/2024 – present | Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Developed a RESTful API to allow for interoperability between different systems.
- Developed Dackend System of a Multiplayer Gaming System With WebSocket.

Full-Stack Web Developer

Innova Infosys

04/2023 - 12/2024 | Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Designed, Developed and Deployed Dynamic Web **Applications**
- Extended and Modified Legacy Applications As Per Demands
- Routinely Debugged and Performed Maintenance on Legacy Application.

Junior Web Developer (LARAVEL, NextJs, MySQL, VueJs) **Ildea Informatics**

04/2022 – 04/2023 | Chittagong, Bangladesh

- Designed and maintained multiple websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and other web technologies.

SKILLS

Programming Language — Java, JavaScript, PHP

Database — MySQL, MongoDB

Backend Frameworks — Spring Boot, Laravel

Frontend Frameworks — ReactJs

CSS Framework — Tailwind, Bootstrap

Others — Git, Docker, Web Scrapping

COURSES

JAVA WITH SPRING AND SPRING BOOT

Pondit

02/2024 - 08/2024 | Dhaka, Bangladesh

Web Application Development

Bangladesh Institute of Technology and Management (BITM) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Shuvo Sarker

Junior Web Developer



in Linkedin 💪 LeetCode 👩 GitHub

L +8801875654219 • Dhaka, Bangladesh

shuvooa707@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Experienced developer with two years of fullstack development expertise. Proven ability to develop and maintain efficient, secure, and scale-able applications for businesses of small to medium sizes using Laravel, MySQL, ReactJs, Java and Spring Boot.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science

World University of Bangladesh 2021 | Dhaka, Bangladesh A lot of Math and unneeded pressure.

LANGUAGES

Bengali — Native Speaker

English — Fluent